Martin Elizbaryan

CONTACT INFORMATION Email: martin.elizbaryan@gmail.com

Address: The 4th Vracakan lane 7 building 51 ap, Yerevan

Phone: +374 93 143 600 Date of birth: Apr 29, 1995 Nationality: Armenian



OBJECTIVE

Hi, my name is Martin Elizbaryan and I'm a full stack developer and tutor in TCO Team. I have had more than

500 students who are now working as a web developers.

I have about 3+ years' experience building websites for clients all over the world

EXPERIENCE

Feb 2020 - Present Laravel Developer

TCO Team

Sep 2019 - Feb 2020 Laravel Developer

M&D Systems

Jan 2019 - Sep 2019 PHP Developer

IFC Markets

Jan 2019 - Dec 2019 **Tutor**

Profit Development Company

EDUCATION

2012 - 2018 Bachelor of Cybernetics

National Polytechnic University Of Armenia

Mar 2022 - Jul 2022 Full stack JS Internship

Armenian Code Academy and Simply Technologies

LANGUAGES

English

SKILLS

Armenian Html Css

Bootstrap Material UI

Russian JavaScript jQuery

VueJS ReactJS
Php MySql
Laravel Node JS
Prisma Git

PROJECTS https://www.ifcmarkets.com/

https://private.ifcmarkets.com/en/login

https://sertx.eu/login

GITHUB

https://github.com/MartinElizbaryan